- Are you ready, kids?
- 孩子们，你们准备好了吗？
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- I can't hear you.
- 我听不到你说话。
all:
Aye, aye, Captain!
全部：
是啊是啊，队长！
- ♪ Ohh... ♪
- ♪ 哦...♪
♪ Who lives in a pineapple
under the sea? ♪
♪ 谁住在菠萝里
在海底？ ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Absorbent and yellow
and porous is he ♪
- ♪ 吸水性和黄色
他是多孔的 ♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ If nautical nonsense
be something you wish ♪
- ♪ 如果航海废话
成为你想要的东西♪
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
- ♪ Then drop on the deck
and flop like a fish ♪
- ♪ 然后落在甲板上
然后像鱼一样扑通扑通♪
all: SpongeBob SquarePants!
- Ready?
所有：海绵宝宝！
- 准备好？
all:
SpongeBob SquarePants!
全部：
海绵宝宝！
SpongeBob SquarePants!
- SpongeBob
- 海绵宝宝
SquarePants!
方裤！
[laughing]
[笑]
♪ ♪
[waves crashing]
[海浪拍打]
[mellow music]
[柔和的音乐]
♪ ♪
[adventurous music]
[冒险音乐]
- Are you ready
for a bedtime story, Gary?
- 你准备好了吗
睡前故事，加里？
- [meowing, yawns]
- [喵喵叫，打哈欠]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
[embellished accent]
Good evening, Gary,
[装饰口音]
晚上好，加里，
and welcome
to Patstarpiece Theatre.
欢迎
前往 Patstarpiece 剧院。
- Hot, hot, hot!
- 热，热，热！
- Hmm, would you like
to hear an exciting story
- 嗯，你愿意吗
听到一个激动人心的故事
about brave Sir Patrick
and the fire-breathing dragon?
关于勇敢的帕特里克爵士
还有喷火龙？
[dragon roaring]
[龙吼]
- [meows]
- [grunts]
- [喵]
- [咕哝]
Or perhaps a thrilling tale
of Explorer Patrick
或者也许是一个惊心动魄的故事
探险家帕特里克
on safari in the jungle?
去丛林探险？
- [roaring]
- [screaming]
- [咆哮]
- [尖叫]
[breathing heavily]
[呼吸粗重]
- [meows]
- [喵]
- Ah!
- 啊！
This is a good one!
"Swamp Mates,"
这是一件好事！
《沼泽伙伴》
a story of two buffoons
in a bog!
两个小丑的故事
在沼泽里！
[laughter]
[笑声]
[cringes]
[畏缩]
Once upon a time,
曾几何时，
there was a saucy superhero
有一个俏皮的超级英雄
with a pugnacious posterior
好斗的后部
and they called him,
"Bubble Bass."
他们称他为：
“泡泡鲈鱼。”
[alarm blaring, screaming]
[警报响起，尖叫]
- [laughs menacingly]
- [威胁性地笑]
- Stop, thief!
- 住手，小偷！
- Hmm.
- 唔。
Hmm.
唔。
- [laughing]
- [笑]
- Excellent job capturing
Man Ray last week, Bubble Bass.
- 出色的工作捕捉
曼雷上周，泡泡巴斯。
- Thank you, Anchor Man.
- 谢谢你，主播。
He was no match
for my mighty hiney.
他不是对手
为了我强大的海妮。
- Hmm.
- 唔。
- [clears throat]
I call this meeting
- [清喉咙]
我称这次会议为
of the Guild of Obsessive Fans,
AKA G.O.O.F's,
狂热粉丝公会的成员，
又名 G.O.O.F，
to order!
Fellow heroes,
来订购！
英雄同胞们，
let us welcome our
newest member, Wonder Whale!
让我们欢迎我们的
新成员，神奇鲸鱼！
- Hmm?
- 唔？
- [clicks tongue]
- [咔嚓舌头]
It would appear
Wonder Whale is late!
就会出现
神奇鲸鱼迟到了！
[beeping]
- Heroes!
[嘟嘟声]
- 英雄们！
- It's the chief!
- 这是酋长！
- Wonder Whale isn't late.
- 神奇鲸鱼没有迟到。
She's been kidnapped
她被绑架了
by the nefarious ne'er-dowell,
邪恶的ne'er-dowell，
HooDoo GooRoo
the VooDoo Villain!
胡都咕噜
巫毒恶棍！
[all gasping]
[全都喘气]
- [yelps]
- [尖叫声]
- [grunts] Don't worry, Chief.
- [咕哝]别担心，酋长。
We'll rescue Wonder Whale--
我们会拯救神奇鲸鱼——
[banging]
- Bubble Bass!
[砰砰]
- 泡泡鲈鱼！
- Mother?
- 母亲？
- Ah! Your mother!
[whimpers]
- 啊！你的母亲！
[呜咽]
- [groans]
- [呻吟]
- Why don't you go outside
and make some real friends?
- 你为什么不出去
并结交一些真正的朋友？
- Mother, you know direct
sunlight gives me gas.
- 妈妈，你直接知道
阳光给我气体。
[belches]
Besides, I'm busy looking
[打嗝]
另外，我正忙着寻找
for my Wonder Whale
action figure.
为了我的神奇鲸鱼
动作人物。
- I knew you'd say
something like that,
- 我就知道你会说
类似的东西，
so your mother has scheduled
a play date for you.
所以你妈妈已经安排了
给你一个玩耍的约会。
- I'm not 23 anymore, Mother.
- 我不再是 23 岁了，妈妈。
You'll just have to cancel it.
- It's too late!
你只需要取消它即可。
- 太晚了！
Your new friend
is already here.
你的新朋友
已经在这里了。
Have fun!
玩得开心！
- Huh?
- Hi ya, buddy!
- 啊？
- 嗨，伙计！
Ready for our play date?
准备好我们的玩耍约会了吗？
- I will not associate
- 我不会交往
with such a dimwitted doofus.
和这样一个傻瓜。
- Aw, you're just saying that.
- 哦，你只是这么说。
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
[grunts, gasps]
[咕哝声，喘气声]
What!
- [laughing]
什么！
- [笑]
- Put those down.
- 把那些放下。
My poor little things.
我可怜的小东西。
Don't worry,
Daddy will protect you.
别担心，
爸爸会保护你的。
- [chomping]
- [咀嚼]
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
You've completely chewed up
my limited edition Anchor Man!
你已经彻底咀嚼了
我的限量版主播！
[growls]
[咆哮]
- Sorry, I'm teething.
- 对不起，我正在长牙。
So, what do you wanna
do for our play date?
那么，你想要什么
我们的玩耍约会做什么？
- Hmph, I have no time
for a cretin like you.
——哼，我没时间
对于像你这样的白痴来说。
I must find my
Wonder Whale action figure!
我必须找到我的
神奇鲸鱼可动人偶！
- Oh!
Oh, I'll help you look.
- 哦！
哦，我帮你看看。
- Stop it, you clod.
=> - 停下来，你这个笨蛋。
Do not touch any
of my property.
请勿触摸任何
我的财产。
- That's okay.
We can play with my game!
- 没关系。
我们可以玩我的游戏！
[grunting]
Let's play Swamp!
[咕噜声]
我们来玩沼泽吧！
- [squeals]
Wait, stop!
- [尖叫声]
等等，停下来！
What are you doing?
[shouts]
你在干什么？
[喊叫]
No!
不！
[crying]
[哭泣]
My precious babies.
我的宝贝们。
- No problem,
I'll fix it.
- 没问题，
我会解决它。
My Wonder Whale!
我的神奇鲸鱼！
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
- I got it!
[groans]
- 我得到了它！
[呻吟]
[dramatic music]
[戏剧音乐]
[wailing]
[哀号]
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
[shouting]
[喊叫]
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
Wonder Whale, where are you?
神奇鲸鱼，你在哪里？
Help!
I...require...
帮助！
我……要求……
assistance.
协助。
- I've got you,
play date partner.
- 我有你，
玩约会伙伴。
Uh, whoa.
呃，哇。
Whoa--
[nervous grumbling]
哇——
[紧张的抱怨]
- [coughing]
- [咳嗽]
Where am I?
我在哪里？
[distant animal shriek]
[远处的动物尖叫声]
By the enchanted spatula
of Suburban Dad.
用魔法抹刀
的郊区爸爸。
We're in a real swamp!
我们正处于真正的沼泽之中！
Ew!
呃！
Why am I wearing
this collar of shame?
为什么我穿着
这耻辱的领子？
- I think it looks good on you.
- 我觉得你穿起来很好看。
- [grunting]
- [咕哝]
Ugh, I despise nature.
唉，我鄙视自然。
- Aw, you just haven't
given it a chance.
- 哦，你只是还没有
给它一个机会。
Smell that swamp air.
闻到沼泽空气的味道。
[inhales]
[吸气]
[gasping]
[喘气]
[sneezes]
[打喷嚏]
- [gasping]
My tongue!
- [喘气]
我的舌头！
Water, give me water.
水，给我水。
Ew!
呃！
Where did you get
this disgusting liquid?
你从哪里得到的
这种恶心的液体？
Whew.
Slimy and refreshing.
呼。
粘稠而清爽。
- This can't be happening.
- 这不可能发生。
This place is a nightmare!
这个地方就是一场噩梦！
I'll never find
my Wonder Whale action figure.
我永远找不到
我的神奇鲸鱼可动人偶。
- [menacing laughter]
- [威胁性的笑声]
- What is that?
- [shudders]
- 那是什么？
- [颤抖]
- [laughing menacingly]
- [威胁性地笑]
- My Wonder Whale!
- 我的神奇鲸鱼！
That crook stole
my precious possession!
那个骗子偷了
我的宝贵财产！
Get him!
抓住他！
- Are we playing tag?
I love tag!
- 我们在玩捉迷藏吗？
我喜欢标签！
[light mellow music]
【轻柔的音乐】
♪ ♪
- [groans]
- Tag, you're it!
- [呻吟]
- 标签，就是你了！
[laughing]
- [menacing laughter]
[笑]
- [威胁性的笑声]
- [gasps]
After him!
- [喘气]
追他！
[both panting]
[两人都气喘吁吁]
- [laughing]
- [笑]
[both panting]
[两人都气喘吁吁]
Whoa-oh-oh! [grunts]
- Where'd he go?
哇哦哦！ [咕哝]
- 他去哪儿了？
- Perhaps he's in that
dilapidated dwelling.
- 也许他就在其中
破旧的住宅。
- I doubt it.
- 我对此表示怀疑。
Maybe he's in that shack?
也许他就在那个小屋里？
[banjo music]
[班卓琴音乐]
[machine hisses]
[机器嘶嘶声]
- Huh.
It's just some uncouth natives.
- 嗯。
这只是一些粗鲁的当地人。
- Hello!
- 你好！
[both grunt]
[两人咕哝]
- I caught these two
a peepin' through the window.
- 我抓住了这两个人
透过窗户偷看。
- They're thieves!
Trying to steal
- 他们是小偷！
试图偷窃
our illegal hot sauce.
我们的非法辣酱。
- Illegal?
- 非法的？
- Our swamp sauce is so spicy
- 我们的沼泽酱太辣了
it can blow
your head clean off.
它可以吹
你的头干净了。
- I assure you
we are not interested
- 我向你保证
我们不感兴趣
in your disgusting hot sauce.
在你恶心的辣酱里。
- Then what's he doing?
- 那他在做什么？
- [gulping]
- [吞咽]
[muffled shouting]
[低声喊叫]
[whistle blaring]
[汽笛声]
- [yelps]
- [尖叫声]
- Huh.
You call that spicy?
- 嗯。
你管这叫辣？
[belches]
[打嗝]
- Back off,
you backwater bumpkins!
- 退后，
你们这些穷乡僻壤！
[dramatic bluegrass music]
[戏剧性的蓝草音乐]
Run!
- [shrieks]
跑步！
- [尖叫]
♪ ♪
- After 'em, boys!
- 追随他们，孩子们！
[both growling]
[双方咆哮]
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
- You ain't a-gettin'
away that easy!
- 你没搞好
走开就这么容易！
- Yee-ha.
- 是啊哈。
- [panting, yelps]
- [气喘吁吁，尖叫]
- Ha, too slow,
you cold-blooded clowns.
- 哈，太慢了，
你们这些冷血的小丑。
[muttering mockingly]
[嘲讽地嘀咕]
Yipe!
哎呀！
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
Those Crocs are catching up
with us!
那些 Crocs 正在迎头赶上
和我们一起！
- [groans]
That hot sauce
- [呻吟]
那个辣酱
has already caught up with me.
已经追上了我。
[belches]
[打嗝]
- [gasps]
That's it!
- [喘气]
就是这样！
- [belching]
- [打嗝]
- What?
- 什么？
[rudder slowing, stops]
[舵减慢，停止]
- [sighs]
So play date partner,
- [叹气]
所以玩约会伙伴，
what are we supposed
to do now. Hmm?
我们应该做什么
现在要做。唔？
- [gurgling]
- [咯咯声]
[laughing]
[笑]
- [menacing laughter]
- [威胁性的笑声]
[sinister music]
[险恶的音乐]
- Give me back my Wonder Whale!
- 把我的神奇鲸鱼还给我！
- Huh?
- 啊？
- Huh? Hey, wait for me, buddy!
- 啊？嘿，等我一下，伙计！
- [laughing]
- Come back here.
- [笑]
- 回到这里。
[panting]
[气喘吁吁]
You'll swing for this,
you ruffian!
你会为此而摇摆，
你这个痞子！
- I am afraid you are
the ones who will swing.
- 恐怕你是
那些会摇摆的人。
[laughing]
[笑]
You ignoramuses fell
right into my trap!
无知的你们堕落了
正好落入我的陷阱！
- Technically, I'm a doofus.
- 从技术上来说，我是个傻瓜。
- HooDoo Guru
the Voodoo Villain!
- HooDoo 大师
巫毒恶棍！
He's real!
他是真实的！
- That's right, Bubble Bass,
- 没错，泡泡巴斯，
and your precious
Wonder Whale is all mine!
和你珍贵的
神奇鲸鱼都是我的了！
- I dread to think
what horrific ritual
- 我不敢想
什么可怕的仪式
you will use it for.
你将用它来。
- Huh? Ritual, shmitual!
- 啊？仪式，什米特！
I just needed it
to complete my collection!
我只是需要它
来完成我的收藏！
- Stealing from
a fellow collector?
- 偷窃
一位收藏家？
That's despicable!
真是卑鄙啊！
I will thrash you, sir!
我要打你，先生！
[grunting]
[咕噜声]
Can't break out.
[bell dings]
无法突破。
[铃声]
- You're probably weak
from hunger.
- 你可能很弱
来自饥饿。
Here, try some
of this spaghetti.
在这里，尝试一些
这个意大利面。
- [slurping]
- [发出声音]
Mmm!
Glorious caloric intake!
嗯！
光荣的热量摄入！
Wherever did you find it?
你在哪里找到的？
- We're sitting on it!
- 我们正坐在上面！
[slurping]
[发出声音]
[both shriek, grunt]
[两人都尖叫、咕哝]
- Ouch.
- [gasps]
- 哎哟。
- [喘气]
Ha ha!
Evil never triumphs
哈哈！
against a truly obsessive fan!
对抗真正的狂热粉丝！
- Yeah!
Evil never triumphs
- 是的！
邪恶永远不会胜利
over a oscillating fan!
在振荡风扇上！
- [groans]
Hm?
- [呻吟]
嗯？
Not so fast, Bubble Bass.
别那么快，泡泡巴斯。
I've got one more trick
up my sleeve.
我还有一招
Or should I say,
up my glove!
或者我应该说，
举起我的手套！
[screaming]
[laughs menacingly]
[尖叫]
[威胁性地笑]
- A Patrick Star action figure?
- 帕特里克明星动作玩偶？
Ha!
No collector would
哈!
没有收藏家会
touch such trash.
碰这样的垃圾。
- Plus, it's a choking hazard.
- 另外，还有窒息的危险。
- [grunts]
- [咕哝]
- What's going on?
- 这是怎么回事？
- That fiend, HooDoo,
is using his magic
- 那个恶魔，HooDoo，
正在使用他的魔法
Voodoo doll powers.
巫毒娃娃的力量。
- [laughing]
- [笑]
[grunts]
[咕哝]
- [choking]
- Sorry.
- [窒息]
- 抱歉。
- I'll take that.
[laughs]
- 我会接受的。
[笑]
[laughing]
[both shouting]
[两人大喊]
- Stop!
I'm allergic
- 停止！
我过敏
to centrifugal force!
到离心力！
- [laughing]
- [笑]
Uh-oh.
呃哦。
- Ha! I'll return this
to its rightful owner.
- 哈！我会归还这个
归其合法所有者。
Me.
- Well done, pal.
我。
- 干得好，朋友。
- Eww.
- 呃。
both:
Huh?
两者：
啊？
- Hey, Luther, Cletus,
- 嘿，路德，克莱特斯，
I found them fellers
what blowed up our still!
我发现他们是家伙
是什么炸毁了我们的蒸馏器！
- Oh, hi!
- 哦，嗨！
- [gargled] Run.
- [漱口]跑。
[dramatic bluegrass music]
[戏剧性的蓝草音乐]
- [whimpering]
[all growling]
- [呜咽]
[全都咆哮]
♪ ♪
- No, our only escape!
- 不，我们唯一的逃脱！
If only I had something
large and buoyant.
如果我有什么就好了
大而有浮力。
- I don't know what
that means, but--
- 我不知道什么
这意味着，但是——
Hop on, friend!
加油，朋友！
- Friend?
- 朋友？
- Sure, you're my play date,
right, buddy?
- 当然，你是我的约会对象
对吧，伙计？
- [stammering]
Buddy?
- [结巴]
伙计？
[dramatic classical music]
[戏剧古典音乐]
♪ ♪
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
- It's over, Bubble Bass!
Give up!
- 结束了，泡泡巴斯！
放弃！
- You will never win, Voodoo,
- 你永远不会赢，巫毒，
because we have the power
of reluctant friendship!
因为我们有力量
不情愿的友谊！
[all gasp]
[全都喘气]
- Yeah, that's right.
- 是的，没错。
Run away from
our righteous acquaintance!
逃离
我们的正义相识！
- Uh, they might
be running from that.
- 呃，他们可能
逃离那个。
- [screams]
- [尖叫]
[both scream]
[两人尖叫]
♪ ♪
- [gasps]
- [喘气]
- What happened?
- 发生了什么？
- Oh, you were dead
for like ten minutes.
- 哦，你死了
大约十分钟。
- Oh, it was all
just a hallucination?
- 哦，就这样了
只是幻觉？
Then my Wonder Whale
action figure
然后是我的神奇鲸鱼
动作人物
is still missing.
仍然失踪。
- Well, you may have
lost your toy,
- 嗯，你可能有
你的玩具丢了，
but you've gained
an indoor pool!
但你已经获得了
一个室内游泳池！
Congratulations!
恭喜！
- [gasps]
My precious Wonder Whale!
- [喘气]
我珍贵的神奇鲸鱼！
- Bubble Bass!
- 泡泡鲈鱼！
What did you do
to my basement?
你做了什么
到我的地下室？
- Perhaps the swamp
wasn't so bad after all.
- 也许是沼泽
毕竟没那么糟糕。
[downtrodden music]
[压抑的音乐]
- Best play date ever!
- 有史以来最好的玩耍日期！
- [laughs]
Whoo-hoo!
- [笑]
呼呼！
This completes my collection.
[laughing]
这完成了我的收藏。
[笑]
- [mechanical laughter]
- [机械笑声]
- Ta-da!
- 哒哒！
I did it,
I did it, I did it!
我做到了，
我做到了，我做到了！
I--whoa--
[crashing]
我——哇——
[崩溃]
- [meows]
- I learned a magic trick!
- [喵]
- 我学会了一个魔术！
Sorry, Gary,
but I've been trying to learn
对不起，加里，
但我一直在努力学习
this trick since
I was a SpongeBoy!
这个伎俩自从
我是海绵宝宝！
[gasps]
- [meows]
[喘气]
- [喵]
- I gotta show Patrick!
- 我得让帕特里克看看！
[laughs]
[笑]
Patrick, come out,
I gotta show you something!
帕特里克，出来吧，
我得给你看点东西！
Patrick!
帕特里克！
He's not home.
他不在家。
Oh!
Squidward!
哦！
章鱼哥！
- [gasps]
- Squidward!
- [喘气]
- 章鱼哥！
Squidward, Squidward,
Squidward, Squidward...
章鱼哥，章鱼哥，
章鱼哥，章鱼哥……
- If he thinks I'm out,
he'll go away.
- 如果他认为我出局了
他会走开。
- Squidward, Squidward!
- [grunting]
- 章鱼哥，章鱼哥！
- [咕哝]
- Squidward!
- 章鱼哥！
I'm so glad you're home.
我很高兴你回家了。
Got a magic trick to show ya.
我有一个魔术表演给你看。
- I...hate magic.
- 我...讨厌魔法。
- How could anyone hate magic?
It's...
- 怎么会有人讨厌魔法呢？
它是...
magical.
神奇。
- [sighs]
Okay.
- [叹气]
好的。
Show me the trick.
给我看看技巧。
- [laughs]
- [笑]
- [groans]
- Pick a card!
- [呻吟]
- 选择一张卡！
Oh.
哦。
[grunts]
[咕哝]
[gulps]
[吞咽]
[humming]
- Watch closely, Squidward.
[嗡嗡声]
- 仔细观察，章鱼哥。
The hand is quicker
than the eye!
手比较快
比眼睛！
- Can't watch, no eyes.
Sorry.
- 无法观看，没有眼睛。
对不起。
- Oh, I wanna show
my trick to somebody.
- 哦，我想展示
我对某人的伎俩。
[crying]
[哭泣]
- [chuckles, yelps]
- [轻笑，尖叫]
Ow.
噢。
- You're the best driving
student I've ever had, Rodger.
- 你是最棒的驾驶者
我曾经有过一个学生，罗杰。
Kudos!
- [laughs]
荣誉！
- [笑]
- Mrs. Puff!
- 泡芙夫人！
Mrs. Puff?
Mrs. Puff!
泡芙夫人？
泡芙太太！
- Rodger, we have to move now.
- 罗杰，我们现在必须走了。
Punch it!
冲吧！
[chuckles]
I think we lost him.
[笑声]
我想我们失去了他。
- Mrs. Puff,
you gotta see my magic trick!
- 普芙女士，
你一定要看看我的魔术！
[both shouting]
[两人大喊]
Pick a card, any card!
选择一张卡，任何卡！
- Hold on, SpongeBob.
- 坚持住，海绵宝宝。
I have a trick
to show you, first.
我有一个绝招
首先向您展示。
- [shouts]
- [喊叫]
- Sorry, Rodger.
- 对不起，罗杰。
We'll pick this up next week.
我们将在下周再讨论这个问题。
- Wait, Mrs. Puff,
you didn't see my trick.
- 等等，帕夫夫人，
你没有看到我的伎俩。
- Okay, show me
the trick already.
- 好的，给我看看
已经是窍门了。
- Pick a card, any--
- 选一张牌，任意——
[screams]
- [sighs]
[尖叫声]
- [叹气]
- [yelling]
- [大喊]
Sandy!
沙！
Sandy, I gotta show you this!
桑迪，我得给你看这个！
Pick a card, any card!
[shouting]
选择一张卡，任何卡！
[喊叫]
Sandy?
沙？
Where's your head?
你的头在哪儿？
- Oh, sorry, SpongeBob,
didn't mean to spook ya.
- 哦，对不起，海绵宝宝，
无意吓唬你。
My head's in another dimension
我的头在另一个维度
observing.
观察。
Hmm.
唔。
- Oh, okay.
I'll come back later
- 哦好的。
我以后会回来的
when you have a head.
当你有头的时候。
- It should
be back by Thursday.
- 应该
周四之前回来。
Friday at the latest.
最迟星期五。
- [panting]
- [气喘吁吁]
- Who is it?
- 是谁？
- Pick a card, any card!
- [yelps]
- 选择一张卡，任何卡！
- [尖叫声]
[accordion music plays]
[手风琴音乐演奏]
Magic, eh, boy-o?
魔法，呃，男孩？
Is this by any chance
a trick where you produce
这是偶然吗
你产生的一个技巧
money coins from behind
people's ears?
钱币从后面
人们的耳朵？
Wink, wink, hmm?
眨眼，眨眼，嗯？
- No.
- 不。
- Then what's the point?
Hm!
- 那还有什么意义呢？
嗯！
- Ah!
- 啊！
Hi, Fred.
嗨，弗雷德。
I got a magic trick
that's gonna dazzle you.
我有一个魔术
那会让你眼花缭乱。
- Ooh, are you gonna saw
my leg in half,
- 哦，你会看到吗
我的腿分成两半
or make it disappear,
or pull a rabbit out of it?
或者让它消失，
或者从里面拉出一只兔子？
- Uh, no, this isn't going
to involve your leg.
- 呃，不，这不会发生
让你的腿参与进来。
- Oh, gotta go, SpongeBob.
I'm washing my thighs tonight.
- 哦，得走了，海绵宝宝。
今晚我要洗大腿。
My leg!
我的腿！
- [crying]
- [哭泣]
Why won't anyone
watch my trick?
为什么没有人
看我的把戏吗？
[echoing]
Trick, trick, trick.
[回声]
诡计，诡计，诡计。
Hmm...
唔...
Ooh.
哦。
Hey, that gives me an idea!
嘿，这给了我一个主意！
There.
那里。
Good evening, folks.
I am the great Sponge-dini.
晚上好，各位。
我是伟大的海绵迪尼。
Now watch closely.
现在仔细观察。
The hand is quicker
than the eye.
手比较快
比眼睛。
Uh-huh, ha, pick a card,
any card.
呵呵，选一张卡吧
任何卡。
[inhales]
[吸气]
[dazzling orchestra music]
[令人眼花缭乱的管弦乐]
♪ ♪
Hm?
嗯？
Ta-da!
哒哒！
Aw, I still wish
Patrick was here to see it.
唉，我还是希望
帕特里克在这里看到了这一点。
- I saw it, SpongeBob!
- 我看到了，海绵宝宝！
It was astonish-able!
真是令人惊讶！
[shouts]
[喊叫]
- Oh, Patrick,
you showed up just in time.
- 哦，帕特里克，
你出现得真及时。
What was your favorite part?
你最喜欢的部分是什么？
- Uh...
- 呃...
my favorite part was...
我最喜欢的部分是...
Ta-da!
哒哒！
I missed everything
before that.
我错过了一切
在那之前。
- Oh, then you
haven't seen anything yet!
- 哦，那你
还没有看到任何东西！
[both yelling]
[两人大喊]
[both laughing]
[两人都笑了]
♪ ♪